Store arrival times in csv file:
  every time a bus is supposed to arrive make a request to the server

Server running, obtaining data using APIs and web-scraping:
  -writing all data into csv file line by line

Python requests training set from server, and server returns csv data file to Python

Python cleans data set to be used as the train set

Python algorithm trains neural network and determines synapses weighting

Weights are then used to predict if a bus will arrive late based and the certainty is returned to the user